{
    "subject": "resource/Cincinnati_CityBeat",
    "predicate": "property/headquarters",
    "object": "Cincinnati, OH 45202",
    "human_readable": "The headquarters of Cincinnati CityBeat are located at Cincinnati, OH 45202.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9854220151901245,
            "question": "Where are the headquarters of Cincinnati CityBeat located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9847597479820251,
            "question": "In which city is the Cincinnati CityBeat headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9837878942489624,
            "question": "Is Cincinnati CityBeat headquartered in Ohio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9810382723808289,
            "question": "Provide the full address of the Cincinnati CityBeat headquarters."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9783615469932556,
            "question": "What city and state are the Cincinnati CityBeat headquarters located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9754924774169922,
            "question": "What state are the Cincinnati CityBeat headquarters in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9691559672355652,
            "question": "Where can I find the Cincinnati CityBeat headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9329758882522583,
            "question": "If you were to visit the Cincinnati CityBeat headquarters, what city would you be in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9129768013954163,
            "question": "What is the zip code of the Cincinnati CityBeat headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8750792741775513,
            "question": "What is the postal code for the Cincinnati CityBeat headquarters?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The headquarters of Cincinnati CityBeat are located at Cincinnati, OH 45202.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2019_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the zip code of the Cincinnati CityBeat headquarters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2019_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were to visit the Cincinnati CityBeat headquarters, what city would you be in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2019_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I find the Cincinnati CityBeat headquarters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2019_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2019_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2019_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2019_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2019_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2019_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2019_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2019_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2019_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2019_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2019_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context states that the headquarters of Cincinnati CityBeat are located in Cincinnati, Ohio, with a specific address given as \"811 Race St, Cincinnati, OH 45202\". This supports the query stating that the headquarters are located at Cincinnati, OH 45202."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}